profilepic.com 2019-06-19

# ProfilePic.com - No.1 UK Dating Site - 100% Free Dating

### This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Policy Date - **25th May 2018 00:01 AM** (GDPR Compliance).   
Revision 2018.A - **3rd June 2018 at 01:54 AM**

We offer our users an optional choice of importing contacts from Outlook, Google Mail, Yahoo mail and other services to send invitation emails to your recipients. 

-Import E-mails from your e-mail provider 

-Store contacts on our database for later use 

-Send emails on your behalf as you to your contacts 

Christopher James McGough <sumitgood[/at/]icloud.com>

### Cookies Policy

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.   
Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users that are based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites across the Internet.   
Users may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/).) 

### Types of Data collected

The owner does not provide a list of Personal Data types collected. Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection. The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application. Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility. 

Mode and place of processing the Data Method of processing The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. 

The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. 

Place The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller. 

### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal. The use of the collected Data The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Access to third party services' accounts. The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document. 

### Information we ask of our users during sign-up and or during use of our service

* marks as non-public information. 

  * **Access Friend/Email Contacts***  
Provides access to any friend or Email contacts the user created
  * **Birthday***  
Provides access to the birthday. While birthday is non-public, your age will be visible to other users. 
  * **Contact email***  
Access the user's contact email address. 
  * **City/Country**  
Provides access to the user's city/country. Publicly displayed. 
  * **Photos**   
Provides access to the photos the user has uploaded. Publicly Displayed 
  * **Share**   
Users may share content on or from our service. We hold no liability for content shared either on site or off site. 
  * **Favourite Music Video/Youtube Video**   
Users may choose to share a music video or youtube video on their profile page which will be public. 

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services: Access to third party services' accounts Additional information about Data collection and processing 

### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services. Additional Information about User's Personal Data In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data. 

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address) and cross-referenced associated ISP / Network to aid spam-bot / rogue actor removal during picture approval processes. 

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information. 

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above. This Application does not support “do not track” requests. To understand if any of the third party services it uses honor the “do not track” requests, please read their privacy policies. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users. Information about this privacy policy 

### GDPR Compliance

In order for this service to be GDPR compliant the following are in effect since 25th of may 2018. 

\- ALL users must opt-in to e-mail marketing with the option of opting-out. 

\- Accounts may be deleted at user discretion and information will be held for purpose of crime prevention only. 

\- ALL users have the option to opt-in or opt-out personlized advertising.   

EOF 

Back

**ProfilePic.com - No.1 UK Dating Site - 100% Free Dating**   
Chat to Single Women and Men on our FREE UK Dating Site, London Dating Site, Birmingham Dating Site, Nottingham Dating Site, Newcastle Dating Site, meet hot women, meet hot girls
